<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HIPO</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HIPO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 08:45:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>/gettingstarted/principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 09:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gettingstarted/principles/</guid>
      <description>HIPO is being developed with 2 main principles in mind:
ez2use &amp;amp; ez2dev HIPO is aimed to researchers without any IT or programming background. This means that the toolset must be as easy to install, setup and use as possible. At the same time, HIPO is being developed actively by one single person (José Verdú Díaz), which limits the amount of work that can be made. Furthermore, this project shall focus on creating new and useful features as actively as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install</title>
      <link>/gettingstarted/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 09:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gettingstarted/install/</guid>
      <description>You will need Python and some modules to use HIPO. If you are not an experienced user you will find detailed instructions in the Environment section. Otherwise, feel free to jump to the Source Code section.
Environment It is recommended to use Conda for installing Python and the required modules. From Conda documentation:
 Conda is an open source package management system and environment management system that runs on Windows, macOS and Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workflow</title>
      <link>/gettingstarted/workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 12:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gettingstarted/workflow/</guid>
      <description>Obtaining Data The Hyperion Imaging System by Fluidigm should be used to obtain image data from a tissue sample. Then, the data should be processed with MCD Viewer, a post-acquisition data processing software provided by Fluidimg to draw regions of interest and export the following three files:
 A .tiff file containing the images of all channels A .txt file containing a brief summary of all channels A .geojson file containing the ROIs  These files must be provided for each sample.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 12:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/credits/</guid>
      <description>Frameworks  Napari: image framework used in HIPO. Hugo: framework used for building this website. Learn: Hugo theme used for this website.  Python Modules  Pandas: data manipulation tool. Pillow: Python imaging library. Tiffile: Python library to work with tiff files. Matplotlib: Python library for creating visualizations. Seaborn: Python data visualization library based on matplotlib. Seaborn-Image: Python image visualization library based on matplotlib, and inspired in seaborn. Tqdm: Python library for printing progress indicators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>